<contentList date="26/10/2020 01:10">
  <content contentuid="hd03949f2gf5ddg4995ga4b2ge6c19ada1cec" version="1">Magic Aura (Advantage)</content>
  <content contentuid="h4cd1b29bg2b68g4edag93eag17903dc2d060" version="1">Magic Aura (Healing)</content>
  <content contentuid="h3ac92584ga7afg46d7ga6fdg1c248c746966" version="1">Magic Aura (Damage)</content>
  <content contentuid="he617ad50g9705g4074gb9a5ge11b1fb04aec" version="1">Animal Understanding</content>
  <content contentuid="haa2a6bafg712dg477egb241gbcdcd360b364" version="1">You may converse with animals.</content>
  <!-- CL27 - NellsRelo Mod Data-->
  <content contentuid="h94ef940dg611bg41a8g84acgfcc9ccff1c7c" version="1">Skeletal Frame</content>
  <content contentuid="h2da4d06eg9f70g4d9bga1ebg40456caad359" version="1">As a Skeleton, poison has no effect on you, though you are vulnerable to Bludgeoning damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5bcb3c31gc511g4bc3gbf7bgde64d29ab296" version="1">Blessing of the Raven Queen</content>
  <content contentuid="h6dc6d54fgbbdeg4b6cgadc8g3922b34328e3" version="1">You gain resistance to all damage until the start of your next turn after using Blessing of the Raven Queen.</content>
  <content contentuid="h944f4b4fg2729g407eg938bg212cef76a9ea" version="1">Intangible Summon.</content><!-- CL_IndestructibleSummon_AI_Ignore -->
  <content contentuid="h8650857ag3b36g4bfdg8270g8b1ad613d9df" version="1">Spell Strike</content>
  <content contentuid="h310edba2gc8a3g4ed1g95f5g4dc2692eb452" version="1">This character is able to add its Wisdom modifier for Melee and Ranged weapon attacks, and deals an additional 1d4 Force damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h081b6aeag04c8g4b18gac40gc2d7dd3cb6c8" version="1">DeathMantle</content> 
  <content contentuid="hd6ca677dgac1dg44c8g8217g1991c20f616f" version="1">Your Necrotic aura becomes thick enough to damage foes who strike you</content>
  <content contentuid="haecff2fbgf630g478cga6d5g0fe1e73b03e1" version="1">Unholy Weapon</content> 
  <content contentuid="hd22bba2egdc74g4118ga101g1176e4e6a351" version="1">Gain Necrotic damage equal to your Wisdom Modifier to your melee attacks</content>
  <content contentuid="hcd3a67eag4adbg4153g9ce9g822e5cfd65d5" version="1">Necrosis</content> 
  <content contentuid="ha6656f5bg2442g4b02g96e0g650352b38d7f" version="1">Oath of the Crown</content>
  <content contentuid="h66810eb1g38f3g40f4g8aedgecb83ad4cf7e" version="1">The Oath of the Crown is sworn to the ideals of civilization, be it the spirit of a nation or fealty to a sovereign. The Knights who swear this Oath dedicate themselves to serving society, and in particular, the just laws that hold society together.
  
  These Paladins are the watchful guardians on the walls, standing against the chaotic tides of barbarism that threaten to tear down all that civilization has built, and are commonly known as Guardians, Exemplars, or Sentinals. Often, Knights who swear this Oath are members of an order of Knighthood in service to a nation or sovereign, and undergo their Oath as part of their admission to the order's ranks.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc8873c54gadb5g48edgb75dg400b616d6168" version="1">Oath of the Crown Tenets</content>
  <content contentuid="h684b40b3g24e0g4c7fg9860g975aef23dd36" version="1">The tenets of the Oath of the Crown are often set by the sovereign to which their oath is sworn, but generally emphasize the following tenets:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Law. The Law is paramount. It is the mortar that holds the stones of civilization together, and it must be respected.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Loyalty. Your word is your bond. Without loyalty, Oaths and Laws are meaningless.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Courage. You must be willing to do what needs to be done for the sake of order, even in the face of overwhelming odds. If you don't act, then who will?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibility. You must deal with the consequences of your actions, and you are responsible for fulfilling your duties and obligations.</content>
  <content contentuid="h987c5b0dg7b16g4a07gacd4g5ac78e018cb7" version="2">Failure to abide by their tenets will result in a paladin forsaking their Oath, and becoming something very different.</content>
  <content contentuid="h095e699fg6737g4e83g9073g022889e8bf75" version="1">Moonlight Strike</content>
  <content contentuid="had63494aga0bfg4a1bg8c61gcafd13746656" version="1">When you make an &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_UnarmedStrike_Monk"&gt;Unarmed Strike&lt;/LSTag&gt; against an opponent, it leaves them under the effects of &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="LIGHT"&gt;Light&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcfc1c8afg02b0g4311g9e3dg73e82f0ed8c4" version="1">Managing the Breath</content>
  <content contentuid="hec252180ge0d0g47e7g9731g69894cad91f2" version="1">Practitioners of the Way of Marshmerrow may utilize their &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="KiPoint"&gt;Ki Points&lt;/LSTag&gt; to imitate some Illusion Spells.</content>
</contentList>
