<contentList date="08/24/2023 01:10">
  <content contentuid="hfcfa0bddg0b81g4fd2gaf53g6053c6032631" version="1">Nightshield</content>
  <content contentuid="hce02e907gb65dg4f69ga64bg1f441e3ed42f" version="1">A protective field of shadowy energy cloaks your body, protecting you from Force damage and Magic Missile, while also granting a bonus to all saving throws. The spell ends if you are exposed to direct sunlight.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb76ab008g2ab4g4fd2g8b99gb3573e3e7e33" version="1">Spell Strike</content>
  <content contentuid="h532ebc21g0637g406fg8cebg44f4cf8ae9bd" version="1">You may add your Wisdom modifier to any melee or ranged attacks you make. In addition, your attacks deal an additional [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="h588da6a0gbe9ag4aa8g9faegfa7fe3d75014" version="1">Fire Shield</content>
  <content contentuid="h4711104bg909dg4fb3gaf30ge644fd97a364" version="1">Thin, wispy flames wreathe your body for the duration, shedding bright light, and providing you with Resistance to Fire damage. Additionally, whenever a creature within Melee range attacks you, the Shield erupts in flame, lashing out at the attacker for [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="he7e3eb29g7383g4012gb659gf77131d8e0fa" version="1">You can end the spell early by using an action to dismiss it.</content>
  <content contentuid="h54b3b9d4gfa42g4825g9f8fg00d30a120328" version="1">Dismiss Fire Shield</content>
  <content contentuid="h36c2a13cg6ccbg4323gbd20gf4ed64fbbd2a" version="1">You dismiss Fire Shield, ending the Status effect.</content>
  <content contentuid="h45049cbbgec84g4f72g8da6g253d56bda198" version="1">Frost Barrier</content>
  <content contentuid="h46522b96g30a2g4d4bg8eb5gaf5af3cb8a3f" version="1">Tendrils of icy air wreathe your body for the duration, reflecting light, and providing you with Resistance to Cold damage. Additionally, whenever a creature within Melee range attacks you, the barrier flings shards of ice at the attacker for [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="h641cfb43g7eaeg4a8fg9817ga12cc9269617" version="1">Dismiss Frost Barrier</content>
  <content contentuid="h8dad3361g84a3g4af7g9557ge5e6673a7ed1" version="1">You dismiss Frost Barrier, ending the Status effect.</content>
  <content contentuid="h15c00300gd39cg40a9g8182g756f1f4bec65" version="1">Lightning Shield</content>
  <content contentuid="hfb5b91f6g4a58g46afgba0ag60b3096f4582" version="1">Snapping sparks surround your body for the duration, giving light, and providing you with Resistance to Lightning damage. Additionally, whenever a creature within Melee range attacks you, the shield electrifies your attacker for [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="h6f55a97agf56fg4052g9f9dg1d28af4c7767" version="1">You can end the spell early by using an action to dismiss it.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4197a67dg94e0g4298gb3c8gdfd03cfc1199" version="1">Dismiss Lightning Shield</content>
  <content contentuid="h24601bdbg1354g4206g8157g72e45f85275c" version="1">You dismiss Lightning Shield, ending the Status effect.</content>
  <content contentuid="h81113385g49d5g4d0ag9fd9g6b5e74f3abf4" version="1">Spelldrinker</content>
  <content contentuid="h6547b6ddg3adeg408dgbc02g9f91bf2b03b2" version="1">An ancient symbol shines over this creature. Whenever a spell attack is made on this creature, it restores a 1st-level Spell Slot.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6cc4593dg5c73g449ag9721g526ad738973c" version="1">For a moment, a phantasmal image of the sign of the Atronach appears around you. For the duration of the spell, whever a spell is cast against you, restore a 1st-Level spell slot.</content>
  <content contentuid="h51b94ed3g01bdg4706g9183gd64620e3b307" version="1">Hearth Heal</content>
  <content contentuid="hdd618935g7de3g4420g9bdbg668fa51c06be" version="1">Healing energy surrounds you, restoring your health by [1].</content>
</contentList>
