<contentList date="08/24/2023 01:10">
  <content contentuid="hef8b663egda40g4814ga8a3g943884629173" version="1">Peaceful Eye</content>
  <content contentuid="hc859716cg3d8cg4c7fgbf10g6397adca8841" version="1">Roaring Palm</content>
  <content contentuid="hb5b16ef5g439bg4b54gbf3cga38398c12c3f" version="1">When using this action, the target must make a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Constitution Saving Throw&lt;/LSTag&gt;. If it fails, it is knocked unconscious. If it succeeds, it takes [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="h4e802633g3b90g42ecg84e2gf18aad9dbb35" version="1">Whenever you use an &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_UnarmedStrike_Monk"&gt;Unarmed Strike&lt;/LSTag&gt; against an opponent, you may spend 6 &lt;LSTag Type="ActionResource" Tooltip="KiPoint"&gt;Ki Points&lt;/LSTag&gt; to spread a 9m radius of pure &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="SILENCED"&gt;silence&lt;/LSTag&gt; centered around your target. In this area, sound will not travel, and any creature within the range cannot speak.</content>
  <content contentuid="he64d5ac5gacc2g4d57gbf01gbf02e40063df" version="1">Calming Gaze</content>
  <content contentuid="h5fc02e1fg9300g4816g9e9cg90a04ee22b86" version="1">Your gaze catches the eye of a creature within range of your choosing. They can make a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Charisma Saving Throw&lt;/LSTag&gt; saving throw. If successful, the spell fails and the creature remains in its emotional state. Otherwise, they will enter a calm state of mind for 8 hours, and refuse to fight. They will also no longer be frightened or Charmed.</content>
  <content contentuid="h31c654d1gb718g4de6g8557gf6c542946349" version="1">Charming Touch</content>
  <content contentuid="h0cc1b517g24f5g4748g937fgc1fa9cec851d" version="1">You touch a nearby creature in an effort to charm it. It must make a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Wisdom Saving Throw&lt;/LSTag&gt; saving throw, and has advantage if you or your companions are fihgting it. If it fails, it is charmed by you for the duration of the spell, or until you or your companions do anything harmful to it. When the spell ends, it will know you have charmed it.</content>
  <content contentuid="h518a5142g4fbbg49ecgb543g6d4722580ae7" version="1">Demoralizing Touch</content>
  <content contentuid="h494276e3g68c0g4630gb5eege914eef8153f" version="1">You touch a nearby creature in an effort to Demoralize it. It must make a Wisdom saving throw. If it fails, it is frightened for the duration of the spell.</content>
  <content contentuid="h96c88250g675fg49d1ga366g0c2e9dfa7e3f" version="1">Frenzying Touch</content>
  <content contentuid="hc8b9bee9g795fg46a6gba32g2e0d6438cc61" version="1">You touch a nearby creature in an effort to rile it up. It must make a Wisdom saving throw. If it fails, it is frenzied for the duration of the spell.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2d19bba1gc532g4419ga081g8a9a12b9ce90" version="1">Heroic Touch</content>
  <content contentuid="h2c5acd82gc94eg4ce1g866bg9a71e98a350a" version="1">You touch a nearby creature in an effort to raise its courage. Until the spell ends, the creature is immune to being frightened, and gains temporary hit points equal to your Spellcasting ability.</content>
  <content contentuid="hfa8c9662gb2e0g4561gba89g7bcb9a5ccf88" version="1">Frenzying Touch</content>
  <content contentuid="hfa8c9662gb2e0g4561gba89g7bcb9a5ccf88" version="1">Frenzying Touch</content>
  <content contentuid="hfa8c9662gb2e0g4561gba89g7bcb9a5ccf88" version="1">Eye-Maze</content>
  <content contentuid="h5c4b6886g1881g4a2aga34eg8a6482aed8f1" version="1">Your body shifts in and out of sight, granting you +2 to AC, and +2 to Stealth.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4e08a7fdgedf9g42eeg9f87g18fe35b02de4" version="1">This creature is only partially visible, granting them +1 Stealth, and an additional +1 AC.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7a2ac713g9ea9g4380gaa4fgb3b12ef0c036" version="1">This creature is only partially visible, granting them +2 Stealth, and an additional +1 AC.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc40199ccgc729g4698g9bbbg88c9a389a67a" version="1">Your body shifts in and out of sight, granting you +1 AC, and +1 Stealth.</content>
  <content contentuid="h839395a4g82dcg49d1ga693g17ae67569315" version="1">Chameleon</content>
  <content contentuid="h5dc2b102g8931g4ebega27fg2ce3afec0bb3" version="1">This creature is only partially visible, granting them Advantage and Proficiency in Stealth rolls.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8b37aac5ge924g47ddg9f9bg0454c9a98db3" version="1">You touch a willing target, causing the coloration and texture of its clothing to blend in with the creature's surroundings. They gain Advantage on and Proficiency in all Stealth rolls.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf1fb07e7g4594g497ag8c4cg55bd93792f36" version="1">Psychic Shock</content>
  <content contentuid="hacda281cg55ebg4339gb592g962c35fc90a0" version="1">You invade another creature's mind, and for one split second, you cause them to perceive some image, noise, or memory that would cause them stress. Choose a target you can see or hear. The creature makes an Intelligence saving throw. If it fails, the creature takes [1], and has Disadvantage on its Attack Rolls this round.</content>
  <content contentuid="h81f6bfeegf3b9g4e47gb406g2a8ac5c7e714" version="1">This creature is reliving a painful memory, and has disadvantage on attack rolls.</content>
  <content contentuid="h252d24e7g4336g443eg80dfg5ac0024ff3a8" version="1">Hush</content>
  <content contentuid="hfc7b1c0aga9f9g4546gacc8g9da25cfe98d9" version="1">You cast an illusion into the mouth of a creature within range. If the creature fails a Wisdom saving throw, no words can come out of their mouth, and their connection to the Weave is severed for the duration of the spell.</content>
  <content contentuid="h35069ed4g06a4g481ag8dfdg03963b207d18" version="1">Skeleton Key</content>
  <content contentuid="h7a726ec1g6911g4cadg8e91g36207c377083" version="1">You poke your finger into the lock, opening any lock.</content>
  <content contentuid="h234b5017g929bg4403g9031gdc09713fbb1a" version="1">Magically teleport up to 9m to an unoccupied space you can see.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbd4ca9b4gf9b3g4f09gbdcbg3791f0d55c8a" version="1">Alter Weapon</content>
  <content contentuid="hd582799ag1ab4g45fega132g97077fa1c873" version="1">While holding a melee weapon, you channel magic into it, altering its properties: Enflame: In addition to its regular attack, your weapon now deals an additional 1d6 Fire damage. | Healing Strike: Your weapon now heals its targets for the damage it would otherwise cause. Undead targets instead take the regular amount as Radiant damage. | Static Bite: Your weapon now deals an additional 1d7 Lightning damage. | Swift Strike: You have advantage on attack rolls with this weapon. | Screaming Cleave: Your weapon now deals an additional 1d6 Thunder damage. | Viscous Tear: Regardless of the weapon's damage type, it now deals an additional 1d8 Slashing damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="hac303a04g7304g4347gb4bagf8c982a0d353" version="1">Enflame</content>
  <content contentuid="h8fe35118gdf18g417ag9711g68cdfd0fdcde" version="1">While holding a weapon, you channel magic into it, altering its properties to deal an additional [1]</content>
  <content contentuid="hc5b32ab2g0c10g4e96ga8d0gdbfe5f463113" version="1">Healing Strike</content>
  <content contentuid="hf9ad20bagea97g4d01g824dgf5a168ad40a4" version="1">While holding a weapon, you channel magic into it, altering its properties to be able to Heal targets for [1], or deal Radiant damage if undead.</content>
  <content contentuid="he88ba08bg809bg4830gbeafge8436c004586" version="1">You may make a Weapon attack to Heal targets for [1], or deal the equivalent amount as Radiant damage to Undead targets.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6bd5856egfa5bg451bg88bcgb4162c288d38" version="1">Static Bite</content>
  <content contentuid="h09447d46gffc8g4cd8gb094gc6582f2a26c5" version="1">While holding a weapon, you channel magic into it, altering its properties to deal an additional [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="h9b72a2e1gbd32g4deag834fgc801ed961ab4" version="1">Swift Strike</content>
  <content contentuid="ha903bd60g9b04g485bgafcdg0000814a42af" version="1">While holding a weapon, you channel magic into it, altering its properties to always give you Advantage when attacking.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1518fe43gb8e7g4a7ag8eb4g257b6e516083" version="1">Screaming Cleave</content>
  <content contentuid="hcc2fae69gf884g4f02g8f42g78463a46a68b" version="1">While holding a weapon, you channel magic into it, altering its properties to deal an additional [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="h0af79943g0d9ag4c81g8751g1490fd5c3cd8" version="1">Vicious Tear</content>
  <content contentuid="h1b7862a6g4ae0g41aag85beg07a9ab8fd7fb" version="1">While holding a weapon, you channel magic into it, altering its properties to deal an additional [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="hadf69a32g4178g4b92ga206gb896e800b661" version="1">This Manifests itself as an extra Action in your hotbar.</content>
  <content contentuid="hfd9fbc4egcaabg4d26ga986g6a3cf65ef932" version="1">Lucksap</content>
  <content contentuid="h2f97f2bag2cedg451agab31g05591f4979d1" version="1">When you cast this spell, you bestow a minor curse on a creature you can see within range. That creature must make a successful Wisdom saving throw, or suffer your choice of on of the following effects for the duration: Foil: The target has disadvantage on Intelligence and Wisdom saving throws. | Fumble: The target has disadvantage on Attack rolls. | Foul: Whenever the target is attacked, they deal an extra [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="h9a51d23bg827dg42cbg9831ga1733b703e12" version="1">Foil</content>
  <content contentuid="h2126970bgfd91g4e07gab97g151c6c93e05a" version="1">This creature has disadvantage on Intelligence and Wisdom saving throws.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5c9386e4g667dg446ega0bdgbc72cca33874" version="1">The target has disadvantage on Intelligence and Wisdom saving throws.</content>
  <content contentuid="h343b02cdgb05cg4cacga587g1e7e29635257" version="1">Fumble</content>
  <content contentuid="h04eb95dbg38fcg453bg8f03gb1afac26b7e0" version="1">This creature has disadvantage on Attack rolls.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9d99cfbcge248g44ffgb2d8g477dc6f6e48f" version="1">The target has disadvantage on Attack rolls.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2d00c05ag4854g48b3g9aaag1f0efc0c7763" version="1">Foul</content>
  <content contentuid="h3b99d74egb2bfg4b6eg83b3gd4b59f8e1b53" version="1">Whenever this creature is attacked, it takes additional damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h578af80bg5ec9g4174gadceg5a4b742a7f90" version="1">Whenever the target is attacked, it takes [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="h6ccf0c85gdc55g4596g90c1gbc45c6d7a222" version="1">Bravery</content>
  <content contentuid="h0b675858ga668g4da9g845egc2c7bdc2c5a3" version="1">This character has advantage on all saving throws against being Frightened.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcae3dba6g66d0g4f1bg8077g507addbc5487" version="1">When you cast this spell, a glittering mantle of courage settles upon a creature you touch. The target has advantage on saving throws against being frightened for the duration.</content>
  <content contentuid="h01828aa6gea5bg4fa7gbbc0g92d5ed31fe51" version="1">Spike Growth</content>
  <content contentuid="h581722bbgb7b9g4b81ga35dg951264bdf258" version="1">The ground twists and sprouts hard spikes and thorns. The area is covered in thorny vines for the duration of the spell.</content>
  <content contentuid="heb0249a6gc1bag4292gb636geabc3e42be7c" version="1">Thundering Armor</content>
  <content contentuid="h72a65006g3bd8g4d09gadfdg7c7a5c941ca2" version="1">You infuse a creature's armor or clothing with pulsing energy, increasing its protection by +2 AC.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3c1867ecg2570g4c3cga989gd89b5e104cc7" version="1">The target also gains the ability sacrifice the spell's effects to blast nearby enemies away.</content>
  <content contentuid="hae17cadeg0d13g4efcgab76g6313e3db81b4" version="1">Release Energy</content>
  <content contentuid="h917114bfg780cg4787ga38ag1953c354fe71" version="1">You release the energy pulsing through your armor from the Thundering Armor into a single creature, dealing [1] and pushing them away.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7ab24283g959bg4fe2g868aga7345a5ad519" version="1">Release Energy (Area)</content>
  <content contentuid="ha257b8aegdd61g43d2gbc90g33242b215c9c" version="1">You release the energy pulsing through your armor from the Thundering Armor, dealing force damage and pushing away nearby creatures.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8198fc32g499fg401ag975eg9d35bf711345" version="1">Misdirected Mark</content>
  <content contentuid="h805bbf01gf211g4215g8ad9ge54594b12e81" version="1">You conceal your arcane attack, mentally influencing your foe into both believing the attack came from one of your allies, and focusing on that ally obsessively. Make a ranged spell attack against a target within range. On a hit, the target takes [1]. As a free action, you choose an Ally who this target will believe made the attack.</content>
  <content contentuid="h392ef12ag8001g4e8cgb07cg7f5374f0e4fc" version="1">Mark Ally</content>
  <content contentuid="hb733faddg6852g45c3ga96fgb491d85b310d" version="1">Using this unlocks a free action to mark an ally.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf9a9f86cg511eg4b2fg984bgcf4739576e84" version="1">Mark an Ally. The target of Misdirected Mark will not have disadvantage on Attack Rolls against this target.</content>
  <content contentuid="hfe63dd0eg49b9g4fe3gbc44gfcca5adc019c" version="1">Muffle</content>
  <content contentuid="he6d4dac1g73aeg46b5g8ba9gd2c5fb511911" version="1">For the duration, all sound created by a target creature or object that you can see within range is muffled. Creatures affected have advantage on any stealth roll.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7d3d70afg88b6g4403g9d58g30dec833dd83" version="1">Lesser Ward</content>
  <content contentuid="h96627ba0gb7deg4d7cg8a8bg06978375f49e" version="1">You are resistant to Bludgeoning damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9d4a0716gce96g43e8gb439g1e4356383243" version="1">The creature you touch is branded with an ancient inscription, granting them resistance to all Bludgeoning damage for 10 minutes.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5567e608gafccg4881gb7cfgabb487e33ad8" version="1">The target of this spell becomes very physically beautiful. A subtle glow surrounds the target in darkness or shadows, and tiny motes of light cling to them in daylight. The target gains advantage on any Charisma checks.</content>
  <content contentuid="h991644b5g2a46g44e7gba7cg45daf9ec2b5b" version="1">HeartStrike</content>
  <content contentuid="ha91ed8ddged86g447agb8aag6363f3a8ee17" version="1">Strike your foes to gain temp hp equal to your Level plus Wisdom Modifier</content>
</contentList>
